<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Motivation &#8211; WeGoGym Blog</title>
	<atom:link href="/post/category/motivation/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link></link>
	<description>Empowering You to Achieve Your Gym Goals</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 02:10:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.7.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Demotivated to Work Out</title>
		<link>/post/demotivated-to-work-out/</link>
					<comments>/post/demotivated-to-work-out/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 00:03:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Motivation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=5</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[After years of going to the gym, one thing has always stood in the way: periods of demotivation. If you’ve ever started working out, you know that the first few weeks are the easiest. It’s new, exciting, feels productive, and you’re motivated to keep going. But eventually, that motivation fades. The problem is that motivation [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>After years of going to the gym, one thing has always stood in the way: periods of demotivation. If you’ve ever started working out, you know that the first few weeks are the easiest. It’s new, exciting, feels productive, and you’re motivated to keep going. But eventually, that motivation fades. The problem is that motivation is a short-term feeling, which is unfortunate because it takes years to build a good physique. </p>



<p>That’s why I created WeGoGym — to make working out easier by giving you the NEED to workout, even when you have no motivation. Over the past year, I’ve helped many friends and family build muscle and lose fat using this method, and I’m excited to help you achieve the same!</p>



<p>Invest in your fitness goals: <a href="https://wegogym.org/">wegogym.org</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/post/demotivated-to-work-out/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
